Who the winny-binny boy?
我的小不點兒
You the winny-winny-binny-binny boy!
你是個小小的小不點兒
Don't cry.
不要哭啊
不要哭嘛
Why is he still crying?
他為什麼還在哭？
Let me hold him for a sec.
我來抱他一下
Here we go.
來，爸爸抱
There we are.
不哭了
Maybe it's me.
或許是因為我
Don't be silly. Ben loves you. He's just being Mr. Cranky Pants.
別傻了，班愛你 他只是愛發牢騷而已
You know,I once dated a Miss Cranky Pants.
我跟一個牢騷小姐約過會呀
Lovely girl. IKind of moody.
好女孩，有點情緒化就是了
There we go,all better.
好了，好多了
There's my little boy.
這才是小乖乖
Can I see something?
我可以試一件事嗎？
Cool!
酷哎
He hates me. My nephew hates me!
他恨我，我的姪子恨我
Come on,don't do this.
好啦，不要這樣嘛
What if my own baby hates me? What do I do then?
要是我自己孩子恨我 怎麼辦啊？
Monica,stop! This is nuts.
摩妮卡，你住口好不好？ 你瘋了是不是啊？
Do you know how long it'll be before you have to deal with this?
你知道你還要多久 才會遇到這個問題呢？
You don't even have a boyfriend yet.
我是說你現在連男朋友都沒有
Joey,she does not look fat.
喬伊，她看起來不胖
The One With the Baby on the Bus
-=BT之家DRM小組 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河馬壓縮製作 本字幕為河馬根據R3DVD OCR得來
六人行 第2季 第06集 寶寶落在巴士上了
Here you go.
拿去
Goo,goo,goo!
咕，咕，咕！
That is so funny! Let me see that a sec.
真好笑，那個借我一下
You okay?
你還好吧，羅斯？
I don't know.
不知道
What's in this pie?
餡餅裡有什麼呀？
I don't know. Butter and eggs and flour and lime and kiwi
不知道，奶油，雞蛋，麵粉 萊姆，奇異果跟…
Kiwi? Kiwi?!
奇異果？奇異果？
You said it was a key lime pie.
你說這個是奇萊餡餅
No,I didn't. I said kiwi lime. That's what makes it so special.
不是，我是說奇異果萊姆 所以才會那麼特別
That's what's gonna kill me.
所以我才會死
I'm allergic to kiwi.
我對奇異果過敏
No,you're not. You're allergic to lobster and peanuts and
你才不會呢 你會過敏的是龍蝦，花生跟…
Oh,my God!
天啊
It's definitely getting worse.
越來越嚴重了
Is your tongue swelling up?
你的舌頭腫了嗎？
Either that or my mouth is getting smaller!
要不然就是我的嘴小了
Get your coat. We're going to the hospital.
穿外套，我們現在就到醫院去
-Will he be okay? -He's gotta get a shot.
他不會怎麼樣吧？ 不會，只是得打一針
You know,actually, it's getting better. It is.
事實上我覺得好多了
Let's not go. Anyone up for Scrabble?
沒錯，別去了 誰要玩拼字遊戲啊？
Jacket,now!
去穿外套
What about Ben? We can't bring a baby to the hospital.
但是班怎麼辦呢？ 我們不能帶個寶寶去醫院啊
We'll watch him.
交給我們吧
I don't think so.
恕難從命
I have seven Catholic sisters. I've taken care of hundreds of kids.
幹嘛？我有七個天主教姐妹 我照顧過上百個小孩
Come on,we want to do it. Don't we?
別這樣 我們想幫忙，對不對？
I was gonna play basketball...
拜託，我本來想去打籃球的…
... but I guess that's out the window.
…不過球被丟出窗外去了
If you take him out for a walk, remember to bring his hat.
好，如果你要帶他去散步 記得要幫他戴帽子，好嗎？
There's milk in the refrigerator and diapers in the bag.
冰箱裡還有一些牛奶 尿布在袋子裡
Hat,milk....
帽子，牛奶…
Got it!
懂了
Consider it done!
包在我身上啊
You understood?
你聽得懂嗎？
My uncle Sal has a really big tongue.
懂啊，我沙叔叔就有大舌頭
Is he the one with the beautiful wife?
他是老婆很正的那個
中央公園
You want to hear the song I'm singing this afternoon?
阿秋，要不要聽聽 我今天下午要唱的新歌呢？
I wrote it this morning in the shower.
今天早上洗澡的時候寫的
I'm in the shower And I'm writing a song
我一邊洗澡一邊在寫歌
Stop me if you've heard it
聽過的話請阻止我
My skin is soapy and my hair is wet
我全身泡沫，頭髮濕搭搭
And Tegrin spelled backward is nirget
香皂倒過來是皂香
Rachel,sweetheart, could I see you for a minute?
瑞秋，親愛的 麻煩你過來一下好嗎？
What's up?
什麼事啊？
FYK:
告訴你…
I've decided to pay a professional musician to play here on Sundays.
我決定以後週日的下午 要付錢請一位職業歌手來演出
Her name is Stephanie something. She's supposed to be very good.
她叫什麼芬妮的，很出色的
But what about Phoebe?
但菲比怎麼辦？
It's not that your friend is bad.
瑞秋，你的朋友不是差而已
It's that she's so bad...
她實在是差到…
...she makes me want to put my finger through my eye into my brain...
差到讓我想把手指頭 伸進我的眼睛裡
...and swirl it around.
然後把腦袋攪成漿糊
Okay,so you're not a fan.
那好，你不是她的歌迷
But,I mean,come on. You cannot do this to her.
可是你不能這樣對她嘛
I have to do this to her?
你叫我出面？
Lather,rinse,repeat
塗皂，沖水，再一次…
And lather,rinse,repeat
As needed
視需要而定
We didn't bring enough stuff.
我覺得我們東西沒有帶夠
Did you forget to pack the baby's anvil?
你有沒有記得 把寶寶的止痛藥帶出來？
I'm telling you,it'll be worth it.
我告訴你，這絕對值得
It's a known fact that women love babies.
大家都知道女人最愛寶寶了
Women love guys who love babies. It's the sensitive thing.
女人愛喜歡寶寶的男人 這是感性的問題，懂了嗎？
Aim him at that pack of babes. Maybe one of them will break away.
把他對準那邊那些寶貝 說不定待會兒有一個會過來
Wait,forget them. We got one. Hard left.
不…等一下 算了，正左方
-Give me the baby. -No,I got him.
來，寶寶給我 不要，我要抱
Come on,seriously.
快，我說真的
Oh,seriously,you want him?
你真的要他嗎？
Who is this little cutie-pie?
這個小可愛是誰啊？
Well,don't think me immodest,but...
不要怪我不懂得謙虛，但…
... me.
…我
Want to smell him?
要不要嗅嗅他？
I assume we're talking about the baby?
我想你指的是寶寶吧？
He's got that great baby smell. Get a whiff of his head.
是呀，他的寶寶味好香 嗅嗅他的頭
My uterus just skipped a beat.
我想我的子宮剛剛頓了一下
What'd I tell you?
你看吧
It's great you're doing this.
我覺得你們這樣做很棒
Well,we are great guys.
我們都是很棒的男人
My brother and his boyfriend have been trying to adopt.
我弟弟跟他的男友 試了三年都領養不到孩子
What agency did you two go through?
你們是找哪一家辦的？
But this is my gig.
這是我的表演
This is where I play.
這是我的地盤
My name is written out there in chalk.
我的名字用粉筆寫在外面
You know,you can't just erase chalk.
你不能把粉筆擦掉的
Honey,I'm sorry.
對不起，我很遺憾
And he's going to be paying this woman?
而且他居然還要付這個女人錢
Why doesn't he just give her a throne and a crown?
那他乾脆給她一個寶座 一頂皇冠
And,like,a gold stick with a ball on top?
還有一根上面有球的權杖
Terry is a jerk! That's why we always say,"Terry's a jerk!"
泰利是混蛋，所以我們才會 常說「泰利是混蛋」
That's where that came from.
不然我們幹嘛那麼說
You probably did everything you could.
你說不定已經盡力了
You know what? Let me just see what else I could do.
好吧，這樣讓我看看 還有沒有別的辦法
Just let her go on after Stephanie whatever her name is.
你何不讓她接在 那個叫黛什麼芬的後面唱啊？
You won't be here. You don't pay her.
你又不在這裡，又不付她錢
I don't know.
我不知道
I'll clean the cappuccino machine!
我幫你洗卡布基諾機好了
You don't clean the cappuccino machine?
你不洗卡布基諾機嗎？
Of course I clean it.
我當然會
I mean,I will clean it.
我是說我會清洗
我會清的
All right,fine,fine,fine!
好…
-Done. -Really?
成了 真的？
Who's working for you,babe?
對呀，看誰出馬嘛
Oh,my God! This is so exciting! How much am I gonna get?
天啊，好興奮哦 我會收到多少錢啊？
What?
什麼？
He's paying the people who were playing.
你說他要付錢給演出的人
I meant,he's paying that other woman because she's a professional.
我是說他要付另外那個女人錢 因為她是職業歌手
I'm not gonna be the only one who's not getting paid.
我可不想當那個 唯一沒有收到錢的人
I'm sorry,no!
對不起，不
No,I'm not some sloppy second, you know,charity band.
不，我可不是什麼二流的… 慈善樂團
There are thousands of places in this city...
這個城市裡面有上千個地方…
...where people would pay to hear me play.
…願意付錢聽我來演唱
When I play,I play for me
我為自己而演唱
I don't need your charity
我不需要你的施捨
Thank you!
謝謝
I'm not getting a shot. Maybe they can take the needle...
你說什麼都別想叫我打針 我是說，或許他們可以把…
...and squirt it into my mouth. Like a squirt gun.
…藥水射進我的嘴裡 就像水槍那樣
Hello there. I'm Dr. Carlin.
你們好，我是林醫生
I see someone's having a little allergic reaction.
好像有人有一點點過敏的反應
Doctor,can I see you for just a moment?
對，醫生 我可以單獨跟你談談嗎？
My brother has a slight phobia about needles.
我哥哥有一點點害怕打針
Did you tell him about my squirt gun idea?
你有沒有告訴他 我那個水槍的主意？
My brother,the Ph.D., would like to know...
我的博士哥哥想知道…
...if there's any way to treat this orally?
這個藥有沒有可能用口服的？
Under these circumstances,it has to be an injection,and it has to be now.
在這種情況之下，打針是 避免不了的，而且要馬上打針
So?
怎麼樣？
Go and have a seat. The doctor says it's got to be a needle.
好吧，坐下來 醫生說這一針非打不可
You're just going to have to be brave. Can you do that for me?
所以你一定要勇敢起來 為我這麼做，好不好？
Oh,boy! You are doing so good.
你做得非常好
You want to squeeze my hand?
要不要握緊我的手啊？
Ross,don't squeeze it so hard.
羅斯，不要握得那麼緊
Honey,really. Don't squeeze it so hard!
真的，不要握那麼緊
Let go of my hand!
羅斯，放開我的手
Good plan. Next time we want to pick up women...
還真是個好計劃 下一回想泡妞…
...we should go to the park and make out.
…我們乾脆直接去公園 親熱算了
Taxi! Taxi!
計程車…
Look at that talent.
你看那票妞兒
Just practicing. You're good.
只是在練習，你很行
Carry on.
繼續開吧
Wait,wait,wait!
等等，等等我們
Hey,you. He's just adorable.
他好可愛哦
Can you tell him that? Because he thinks he looks too pink.
告訴他，好不好？ 他覺得他臉色太紅潤了
-What are you guys out doing today? -We're not out.
你們今天出來做什麼？ 我們沒有
We're two heterosexual guys hanging with the son...
我們只是幫我們的 異性戀朋友…
...of our other heterosexual friend, doing the usual straight-guy stuff.
…帶孩子的異性戀男人 做一般男人應該做的事情
You done?
講完了？
There's our stop.
我們到了
Get out of here! This is our stop.
少來了，我們才到了
You guys live around here too?
你們也住在這附近啊？
We live in the building by the sidewalk.
我們住在那個人行道旁邊
You know it?
你們知道嗎？
Since we're neighbors,what do you say we get together for a drink?
對了，既然大家是鄰居嘛 我們聚一聚喝點東西，如何？
So you want to go to Markel's?
我們去馬可咖啡廳，好嗎？
Sure,they love us over there.
好啊，他們很喜歡我們
Where's your baby?
你們的寶寶呢？
Ben! Ben!
班…
That's good. Maybe he'll hear you and pull the cord!
或許他會聽到拉鈴啊
Stop the bus!
停車
Are you sure he didn't break it? It hurts.
你肯定沒有捏斷？我真的很痛
No,it's just a good bone bruise.
沒有，只是有一塊瘀青
And right here is the puncture wound from your ring.
還有這是你戒指壓出來的痕跡
-I'm really sorry. -It's okay.
對不起，我真的很抱歉 沒關係
Sorry.
抱歉…
Sorry! I got my S's back!
抱歉…我說清楚了
Which we can celebrate later.
那我們待會兒再慶祝
Celebrate. Celebrate....
慶祝…
He was a double,double
他是個雙雙雙
Double-jointed boy
雙關節男孩
So are you the professional guitar player?
你就是那個專業的吉他手嗎？
Yeah,I'm Stephanie.
對，我叫黛芬
Right. My name was on there, but now it just says carrot cake.
對，上面本來有我名字的 現在只剩紅蘿蔔糕了
So how many chords do you know?
你會彈幾個和弦？
-All of them. -So you know D?
全都會啊 是嗎？那你會D調
Do you know A-minor?
那你會A小調嗎？
Do you know how to go from D to A-minor?
你會從D和弦轉到A小調嗎？
So does your guitar have a strap?
那你的吉他有背帶嗎？
Mine does.
我的有
Stephanie knows all the chords
黛芬什麼和弦都會
Come on! Pick up,pick up!
快接…
Transit Authority?
運輸中心嗎？
I'm doing research for a book.
我在幫一本書做調查
I was wondering what somebody might do if they left a baby on a city bus.
如果有人把嬰兒留在市公車上 那該怎麼辦呢？
Yes,I realize that would be a stupid character.
是，我知道 只有笨蛋才會這麼做
Here's the deal: We lost a car seat on a bus.
我們今天在公車上 掉了汽車安全座椅
It's white plastic and it fits onto a stroller.
白塑膠材質 有把手，可以用在推車上面
And there was a baby in it.
裡面還有一個嬰兒
He wants to talk to you.
他要跟你講
Everybody,let's give a warm Central Perk welcome to
各位 我們以最熱烈的掌聲歡迎…
Terry's a jerk And he won't let me work
泰利是個混蛋 他不讓我工作
And I hate Central Perk
我恨中央咖啡園
To Stephanie Schiffer!
歡迎史黛芬
I'd like to start with a song I wrote for the first man I ever loved.
首先我想唱一首 我為我的初戀情人寫的歌
Zachary
柴克力…
Are all invited to bite me
被邀來咬我
We're the guys that called about the baby! Is he here?!
我們打過電話來公車上的嬰兒 怎麼樣了？到了沒有…
He's here.
到了
I assume one of you is the father.
你們之中有一個是父親吧
-That's me. -I'm him.
是我 是我
Actually,we're both the father.
事實上呢，我們兩個都是
Oh,Ben! Hey,buddy.
寶貝…
Please tell me you know which one is our baby.
你知道哪個是班嗎？
That one has ducks on his T-shirt and this one has clowns.
那個T恤上有鴨子 這個有小丑
And Ben was definitely wearing ducks.
班絕對是穿著鴨子T恤的
Or clowns.
或小丑
That one's Ben! Remember he had that cute little mole by his mouth!
等一下，那個絕對是班 記得他嘴邊那顆可愛的小痣
Hey,Ben! Remember us?
班，記得我們嗎？
Okay,the mole came off.
天啊，痣掉了
What are we gonna do?
我們該怎麼辦？
We'll flip for it. Ducks or clowns.
丟銅板決定，鴨或小丑
-Flip for the baby? -You got a better idea?
要丟銅板決定 你有更好的主意嗎？
All right,call it in the air.
好吧，在空中叫
Heads.
頭
Heads,it is.
就是頭
We have to assign heads to something!
我們得決定頭是哪一個
Right!
好的！
Ducks is heads because ducks have heads.
鴨子是頭，因為鴨子有頭
What kind of scary-ass clowns came to your birthday?
幫你慶祝生日的小丑沒有頭 不會嚇壞你嗎？
Just call me angel Of the morning,angel
叫我清晨天使
Just touch my cheek Before you leave me,baby
在離開我之前 輕觸我的臉頰
Just call me angel Of the morning,angel
叫我清晨天使
Then slowly turn away
然後轉身離去
I won't beg you to stay
我不會求你留下來
With me
陪我
Here. I thought you might be cold.
來，我想你可能會冷
Thank you.
謝謝
Look at you! You did pretty well.
看看你，幹得不錯嘛
$8. 27.
這裡一共是八塊又二十七分
But not really,because I put in the first two.
其實沒那麼多啦 頭兩塊是我放的
Just to get the ball rolling and to make myself feel better.
只是讓錢滾滾來 還有讓自己舒服一點
Do you?
結果呢？
You know,this whole playing for money thing is so not good for me.
為了錢演奏這碼子事 對我非常的不好
I don't know,when l sang "Su-su-suicide"...
我不知道 當我唱到「自殺」…
... I got,like,$ 1. 75.
…我得到一塊七十五分錢
But then "Smelly Cat"?
可是「臭臭貓」呢？
I got 25 cents and a condom.
二十五分錢跟一個保險套
So,you know,now I just feel really bad for "Smelly Cat."
所以現在我為「臭臭貓」 感到很難過
Honey,I don't think everybody gets "Smelly Cat."
我不認為 大家都會懂「臭臭貓」啊
I mean,if all you've ever actually had are healthy pets,then whoosh!
我是說 如果你只要養過健康的貓的話
But it's not even that,you know?
可是根本就不是那個嘛
I used to do my songs because it made me happy.
本來我唱歌只是因為我很高興
Now it's just all about the money,you know?
可是現在卻變成全都是為了錢
Well,people missed you in there.
菲比，大家都很想你
In fact,there was actually a request for "Smelly Cat."
事實上 還有人指名要聽「臭臭貓」呢
Really? From who?
真的啊？是誰呢？
Well,me.
我啊，就是我
And I know it's not your big money song,but it's my favorite.
我知道那不是賺大錢的歌 但我最喜歡的就是那首
Did I accidentally drop a condom in your case?
我是不是 不小心丟了一個保險套啊？
It's kind of an emergency.
情況緊急嘛
-Here you go. -Thanks a lot.
拿去吧 謝了
Hey,Christine! I got it!
克麗絲，拿到了
I want to thank you for being there for me.
我只是想要謝謝你今天的幫忙
And I'm sorry I almost broke your hand.
對不起，我差點捏斷你的手
That's okay. I'm sorry I poisoned you.
沒關係，抱歉你中了我的毒
Remember the time I jammed that pencil into your hand?
你還記得 我用鉛筆戳你的手那回嗎？
Remember it? What do you think this is,a freckle?
記得嗎？ 你以為這是什麼？雀斑啊
What about the time I hit you in the face with Sylvian's pumpkin?
等等，那我用薇恩的南瓜 打你臉那一次呢？
Remember when I stuck that broom in your spokes...
天啊，記得我把掃把 插進你腳踏車輪裡…
...and you hit your head on the curb?
結果你翻車頭撞到路邊那次嗎
But I remember people telling me about it.
不，我記得 是別人告訴我那件事
I hope Ben has a little sister.
我希望班有個小妹妹
And I hope she can kick his ass.
希望她能夠好好的整整他
I'm gonna get a new Band-Aid.
我去拿一個新的繃帶
How about the time I cut the legs off your Malibu Ken?
我切下 你馬裡布肯娃娃的腿那次呢？
That was you?
是你幹的啊？
They were infected. He wouldn't have made it.
對，它的腿發炎了 不切的話它會死
My little nephew.
我的小姪子
Come here,little one!
過來，小東西
There's my little baby,Ben!
我的小寶貝班班
Hey,he's not crying!
他居然沒有哭
他沒哭呀
There's still pie!
還有餡餅
I'm here. I'm here.
我在，我在
How's my little boy?
我的小寶貝好嗎？
You want Daddy to change your diaper? I know,I know.
要爸爸幫你換尿布，對不對？ 我知道…
Did you have fun with Uncle Joey and Uncle Chandler today?
你今天跟喬伊叔叔 還有錢德叔叔玩得開心嗎？
He rode the bus today.
開心，他今天坐公車了
Big boy riding the bus
好耶，大男生坐公車喔
Hey,I have a question.
我有個問題耶
How come it says, "Property of Human Services"?
他的小屁股上為什麼會有 「服務處財產」這些字？
You are gonna love this.
你一定會覺得很精采的
Can you hold Ben for a sec?
幫我抱一下班，好嗎？
Come here. Come here.
過來…
Stay back! I've got kiwi! Run,Joey,run!
別過來，我有奇異果 跑呀，喬伊
Smelly cat,smelly cat
臭臭貓…
What are they feeding you?
你都吃些什麼啊？
No,no. I'm sorry,it's:
不對…對不起
Smelly cat,smelly cat
臭臭貓…
Better!
好一點了
Much better. Good.
好多了
Don't feel bad, because it's a hard song.
你知道嗎？不要難過 這首歌本來就很難
-You want to try it again? -From the top?
要不要再試一次？ 好，從頭
There is no "top," all right?
這次沒有頭，好嗎？
That's the beauty of "Smelly Cat."
那是「臭臭貓」的美妙之處
Why don't you just follow me.
你跟著我唱好了 好
Smelly cat,smelly cat
臭臭貓…
What are they feeding you?
他們餵你什麼？
Smelly cat,smelly cat
臭臭貓，臭臭貓
It's not your fault
不是你的錯
That's too much. Sorry.
太誇張了，對不起